<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:card_view="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">



    <android.support.v7.widget.CardView

        android:id="@+id/card_view"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:layout_margin="10dp"

        card_view:cardBackgroundColor="@color/white_color"
        card_view:cardElevation="4dp">
        <ScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content">
            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical">


                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="20dp"
                    android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
                    android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
                    android:text="Privacy Policy:"
                    android:textColor="#000"
                    android:textSize="@dimen/textsize"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="20dp"/>


                <TextView
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                    android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
                    android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
                    android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
                    android:text="Health Management Associates is committed to protecting the privacy and security of visitors to our website.\nHealth Management Associates does not collect any personally identifiable information on our website, except in cases where the visitor offers it voluntarily for the purpose of receiving additional information or registering for a service. We use this information solely to respond to and process the request, and we do not share or otherwise disclose any personal information, including your name, address, or email addresses with other organizations.\nOur server records domain names, including client host name and user name, solely for internal purposes intended to improve the user’s experience. We analyze our website logs to periodically improve our website and to tailor it to the needs of our visitors. We do not gather, request, record, require, collect or track any Internet users’ personally identifiable information, and we do not disclose any information to third parties or permit third parties to set and access cookies on your computer through our site.\nWe have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information which is collected through our site."
                    android:textSize="@dimen/textsize"
                    android:layout_marginBottom="20dp"/>

            </LinearLayout>
        </ScrollView>

    </android.support.v7.widget.CardView>








</RelativeLayout>
